{
    "id": "189ac26d575743b996215981a942386f",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I couldnâ€™t understand a word of what he said.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "make out",
                "bring out",
                "come out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The young man has planned to save some money each month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "turn up",
                "put by",
                "put up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The chairman invited the speaker to present his arguments",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "brought out",
                "called upon",
                "called off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked the boy to examine his work carefully.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "give in",
                "go through",
                "make off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog looked as if it was about to attack me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go for",
                "go in for",
                "go on with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Dogs seldom tolerate cats because the cats are capable of harming them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go with",
                "put up with",
                "put by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The terrorists finally surrendered after fighting continuously for twenty four hours.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gave in",
                "gave away",
                "passed away"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The Mayor distributed the prizes at the sports meet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gave in",
                "gave away",
                "gave out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His irresponsible habits caused his ruin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "brought out",
                "brought about",
                "got around"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "An Ad Hoc committee has been established by the government to look into the matter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "put up",
                "set up",
                "set off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}